https://www.nsawins.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentUSA Players: Bet Sports at Bovada and get $250 FREE on 1st Deposit!
Menu HomeAbout UsFAQsTestimonialsContact UsLoginFree PicksFree Picks from The LEGENDFree Picks from BLACK CARD CLUBFree Picks from Free-Picks.com!Best BetsThe LEGEND’s Best Bets Today!Horse Racing PicksNFL PicksCollege Football PicksNBA PicksCollege Basketball PicksMLB PicksNHL PicksHorse PicksToday’s Horse Racing BEST BETS!Saratoga PicksBelmont Park PicksGulfstream Park PicksSanta Anita Park PicksChurchill Downs PicksLos Alamitos PicksGolden Gate Fields PicksOaklawn Park PicksWill Rogers Downs PicksBlack Card ClubOddsNFL OddsSuper Bowl OddsCollege Football OddsNational Championship OddsNBA OddsNBA Finals OddsCollege Basketball OddsNCAA Basketball Title OddsMLB OddsWorld Series OddsNHL OddsStanley Cup OddsPGA OddsNASCAR OddsHorse Racing OddsSoccer OddsBoxing OddsUFC OddsTennis OddseSports Odds2020 Presidential ElectionSportsbooksBest Sportsbooks OverallRecommended USA SportsbooksExclusive Sportsbook BonusesBest Casinos ListBest Casino BonusesBest Poker Sites ListBlog
Menu HomeAbout UsFAQsTestimonialsContact UsLoginFree PicksFree Picks from The LEGENDFree Picks from BLACK CARD CLUBFree Picks from Free-Picks.com!Best BetsThe LEGEND’s Best Bets Today!Horse Racing PicksNFL PicksCollege Football PicksNBA PicksCollege Basketball PicksMLB PicksNHL PicksHorse PicksToday’s Horse Racing BEST BETS!Saratoga PicksBelmont Park PicksGulfstream Park PicksSanta Anita Park PicksChurchill Downs PicksLos Alamitos PicksGolden Gate Fields PicksOaklawn Park PicksWill Rogers Downs PicksBlack Card ClubOddsNFL OddsSuper Bowl OddsCollege Football OddsNational Championship OddsNBA OddsNBA Finals OddsCollege Basketball OddsNCAA Basketball Title OddsMLB OddsWorld Series OddsNHL OddsStanley Cup OddsPGA OddsNASCAR OddsHorse Racing OddsSoccer OddsBoxing OddsUFC OddsTennis OddseSports Odds2020 Presidential ElectionSportsbooksBest Sportsbooks OverallRecommended USA SportsbooksExclusive Sportsbook BonusesBest Casinos ListBest Casino BonusesBest Poker Sites ListBlogYour privacy is very important to us. At NSAwins.com, we are committed to undertaking substantial measures to protect the privacy, accuracy, and reliability of your personal information and to protect such information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Please read the following description of our policies and practices regarding your personal information.We may request personal information from visitors such as name, home address, e-mail address, age, income, interests and gender for purposes such as newsletters, contests, opinion polls, and registration, and for participation in other interactive online activities. We do not request sensitive personal information, such as racial or ethnic origin or health or medical data. We will NOT share mailing list information with other businesses outside of the NSA Enterprises L.L.C. family of websites/companies. This currently includes: www.nsawins.com and www.vegassi.com. This list is subject to change. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out of our mailing list, please email us at feedback@nsawins.com.From time to time, we may place a “cookie” on your computer. A cookie is a file written to your computer’s hard drive that records certain technical information about your Internet usage, such as your IP address, browser type, or domain name. Also, if you submit personal information to our web site (such as your name, interests or preferences), we may use cookies to keep track of such information so that you will not need to reenter this information during subsequent visits. We use cookies to customize delivery of our web site content and advertisements. You may set your Internet browser preferences to notify you when you receive a cookie or decline acceptance of cookies. If you decline acceptance of cookies, however, you may experience less than optimal performance of our web site.NSAwins.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your NSAwins.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.If you have any comments or questions about the information you have submitted on this web site, including its accuracy or integrity, or if you wish to access and verify such information, you may send an e-mail to feedback@nsawins.com. You may also call us at 1-866-444-8427.Help Us Share Our Site, NSAwins.com, on Social Media, Thank You!Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pinterest (Opens in new window)Click to share on Reddit (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)EXCLUSIVE Free Picks!Get Exclusive FREE PICKS from Sonny LaFouchi(aka The LEGEND) sent to your email! Enter email and submit.BEST BETS & Free Picks!The LEGEND WON Again Last Night! 3 College Football Vegas Smart Money BEST BETS Friday Night to BOOST YOUR BANKROLL for the Weekend!December 10, 2020Horse Racing Picks on Friday – Gulfstream Park, Aqueduct, Los Alamitos & Turfway Park. 12 BEST BETS and W/P/S ALL 35 Races!December 10, 2020NFL Week 14 Odds and Schedule – Latest Vegas Betting Odds for 2020 NFL Week 14 ActionDecember 10, 2020Vegas Black Card Club 3-0 Last Night, EN FUEGO! NFL Patriots @ Rams plus CFB Fla Atlantic @ So Miss and Pitt @ Ga Tech BIG PLAYER LOCKS Tonight!December 10, 2020The LEGEND Absolutely OWNS Thursday Night’s NFL & College Football Board! VIP Patriots @ Rams Vegas WISEGUY INFORMATION LOCK! $$$.December 9, 2020Horse Racing Picks on Thursday – Gulfstream Park, Aqueduct, Los Alamitos & Turfway Park. 12 BEST BETS and W/P/S ALL 35 Races!December 9, 2020TOP USA SPORTSBOOKS!#1  Bovada#2  Intertops#3  GT Bets#4  AmericasBookie#5  MyBookiePay Per Head@nsawins on TwitterMy TweetsAmerica’s BookieMember Testimonials“Superb service that I would recommend to anyone considering signing up.” – George Y. from Springield, MA
“I am a big fan and have recommended your service to a number of my co-workers and friends. Stay grooving baby!” – Wayne V. from Palm Beach, FL
“Fantastic service and excellent customer service on top of it.” – Cheryl G. from Carmel, IN
“It’s been great doing business with an honest service.” – William W. from Macon, GA
"Sonny, you are the man! Drinks are on me when I go back to Vegas! Let's stay hot my man." - Brian T. from Phoenix, AZList of BEST USA Betting SitesLike to Bet On Sports? Check our list of Best USA Sportsbooks for Online & Mobile Betting!Are you a Poker Player? Check our list of 3 Best Online Poker Rooms for USA Players!Best Pay Per Head Books! Pay Per Head @ RealBookies.comLooking for some FREE Casino Cash? Check our list of Online Casino Bonuses!Check out USA Betting for more great betting sites.Gambling Problem? Call 1-800-GAMBLER or visit the National Council on Problem Gambling at www.ncpgambling.orgBet on NCAA Football with BOVADA and get $250 FREE on 1st Deposit!
Scroll back to top
